Include your party chat audio when you
broadcast gameplay with Twitch.
While you’re in a party and playing a game,
snap Twitch, select Broadcast, and choose Settings.
Check whether the option to broadcast party chat is selected.
Then, start the broadcast.
Each friend in your party can choose
whether to include their chat audio in the broadcast.
In the Party area of the guide,
they’ll see the option Include my audio.
Anyone who does not opt in can still chat with the party,
but their audio won't be included in the broadcast.
Party members on Windows 10 PCs can be included too.
Discover more! Get information and tips from Xbox Help.